I'm not here, I'm not here, I'm not here!
I just wanted to like it.
I'm here to announce today's expedition.
I'd like to announce today's expedition... today's expedition is a chocolate factory... and it's not with Charlie.
Today's expedition is to make homemade Valentine's Day chocolates.
I thought I'd get one.
On the contrary.
I'll take it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We...
We've been indebted to E Beans on a regular basis.
And to show our gratitude...
I made homemade chocolates to present to Mr. Sato.
I made homemade chocolates to present to him.
Eee...
What should I do? It doesn't taste good, so please don't do the show from now on.
No, it's possible. I don't know about that.
First of all, let's get the materials needed to make the chocolate.
Let's go to the 100-yen store on the first basement floor, Wachii, and do some shopping.
I'm off.
I'm Heisei Lovely.
Heisei Lovely.
It has a Heisei cuteness to it.
Our generation
We had a lot of these.
It brings back memories.
I used to buy a lot of these when I was in elementary school.
I'll buy them because I miss them.
Well, I went shopping at Batch and came back home.
Yes, I bought a lot.
Here it is!
Ta-da!
This is amazing!
There were so many things!
I put so many things in my lucky basket!
I'm sure there's something in there that doesn't seem to have anything to do with this.
Is it my imagination?
There's a lot of stuff in here.
It's just my imagination.
I wonder if he's using a "goody" or something.
I don't know... but they have everything.
We've got all kinds of stuff.
We've got all kinds of Valentine's Day stuff.
There's even a corner.
It's been a long time since I've been so excited.
Now that we have all the ingredients
Let's make chocolate!
I'll do my best!
First of all, let's make chocolate.
Break it?
Yes.
It's been so long.
I used to make it every year when I was in elementary school.
But when I was in middle school and high school...
They stopped letting me make it around testing time.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
And it's definitely Valentine's Day.
I guess that's pretty much it.
That's why I can't make it.
It was a ploy on the part of the school.
I think they were there.
To make it less exciting.
Like, "Don't bring the chocolates.
The school board
Like, "You need to study.
I see.
It's terrible, isn't it?
At least let me play the event box.
It's a ticker tape. It's my opinion.
I'm sure you're right.
From a guy's point of view...
Most of them have never made one before.
It's like, "Oh, this is how we do it.
That's true.
They just take what's made.
You just get it.
There's always White Day, right?
One month later.
It's hard to find someone to make that for you.
Maybe not men.
Of course not.
Boys are under a lot of pressure.
To give it back.
I don't know what to give back.
There's no standard... chocolate.
That's true.
What should I give back?
When I give him sweets.
Don't you ever get disappointed?
Girls...
Like they want something from you.
Maybe it's a little weird.
Why do we have to do it hand-to-mouth?
Isn't that it?
See, that's the idea.
You know, it's like...
A little bit higher than what I gave you.
Why not?
It makes me happy.Like, I'm happy for you.
Or like, some kind of nice chocolate.
Ah...
Nice chocolate.
So feelings aren't enough?
No, it's fine.
It's hard being a jerk, isn't it?
Throw in some onigiri.
I put it on.
I miss this.
I've been cleaning the kitchen from morning till night
cleaning the kitchen from morning till night.
Cleaning up afterwards was also a lot of work.
Chocolate?
My mother would get so mad at me.
I'd like to try some.
I miss it.
You know how girls are.
You know, for friends and stuff.
That's right.
You'll bring something for everyone.
It's so much better when you buy it.
I said it.
I'm sure she's sorry she made it.
It's a girl thing.
It's important. It's important.
I bet you all did this at home, too.
Let your mom do most of the work.
You know, just to get the point across.
You know, to get the important stuff out of her.
Well, not your mother.
Your father.
You have good eyesight.
I can imagine.
They're going to let him do it.
Put it in there.
You're gonna put it all in there, aren't you?
What? I'm sorry.
Does it matter how much or how little?
It's fine.
Just warm it up.
That's a start.
Even if there's leftovers.
You'll have to drink the cream.
It's hot, hot, hot.
That's hot!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's too dangerous!
I don't know how much heat to use.
You bring it to a boil, right?
You put it on after that, right?
I see.
It's dangerous.
It's okay.
The side chest is fine.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wrong, wrong, wrong.
What is it with the whipped cream?
It's like drift, for example.
It makes it softer.
Creamy.
Yes, yes, yes.
Once this is cooled.
Marshmallow, what are you doing?
We're gonna use caps.
Bake them.
You do?
You're good.
All over the place.
Oh, my God.
Not at all. This way.
No, it's not.
It's just a tooth.
Just one clean tooth.
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
What are you doing?
No, no, no, I'm trying to do it all over.
I know, right?
Oh, that's dangerous.
It's dangerous!
You don't have to make a spectacle of it.
This thing I'm making now...
It's for you only, right?
Will this be shared? This...
It's okay to share it.
Maybe a little tiny one.
Wow! What is this?
Oh, it looks so good!
Chocolate strawberries, marshmallows and chocolate crunch!
Wow! It's got texture and it's kind of fluffy on the inside.
So I've finished healing.
I'd like to start decorating it!
I'm going to use the core powder, the stick part of this stick, and then I'm going to make a mold.
And I'm going to harden a mold or something like that.
I'm going to use this.
I'm going to use Teasela Grey Pack and
And I'm heating up a pen right now.
Oh, you mean for writing?
Yes. What should I write?Yes, what should I write?
That's where sense comes in.
Of course.
What are you doing?
Yuna-san.
You just took it out of here.
I thought it would be better to have a variety.
What?
Wouldn't it be cuter if there were square ones, too?
Yes, but...
We're going to make homemade choco-preserves.
What? It's handmade.
They're the same kind.
It's Yuna's handmade.
We're in the process of coming up with a name for it.
When we were developing the product...
You're lying!
It's called "melt-in-your-mouth chocolat.
It's so famous!
I've said it before.
What are you gonna do when you take your first bite?
I said, "You're lying.
What if he says it's delicious?
That's funny.
If they're happy with it, that's all that matters.
I think it's important to entertain them.
I think that's important.
No, you're cheating them.
I'm not trying to entertain them.
No, you have to entertain them.
Lying is important too.
If we were honest about everything.
If you're honest about everything, the world won't turn.
If you don't eat it the first time...
Please try this one too.
I shake it up a bit.
Is this one better?
I'll go for it.
What should I do if he says this one tastes better?
What should I do?
It's so small and hard!
I'll try my best.
It looks good!
Sato!
Love!
This is nice!
It's like Valentine's Day, isn't it?
The only thing is that it's not a valentine, but it's a last name.
For Valentine's Day.
"Love" for "Sato"...
It's the most common last name in Japan.
I have it too, if you must know.
That's for sure.
That's true.
You've got to work hard to get Sato out.
Handmade or alive?
See?
I'm sure people will think I made this too.
It's just moist chocolate.
It's a scary face.
A portrait.
You do portraits too, Kan-chan.
Yes, yes, yes!
You're doing great!
You did it!
That's not fair!
Only at the end...
It's like you put it all together.
I'm the type to go with the flow.
She said it!
What's this?
This is Sato.
Sato.
Hang in there, Sato!
Sleep on it!
That's tacky.
Please don't call me lame.
I like you.
And I don't know what your first name is.
Does that mean you're sending me home?
Yes, I do.
When I gave it to you.
I want you to know that it's for your mother.
I'm just saying...
Why the initials?
on the bowl?
I'm writing on the bowl, but it's not coming out.
What kind of elaborate stunt is this?
It's a birthday present.
This is the kind of thing that turns into a birthday!
How stylish!
The plate is so cute!
This is amazing!
I feel like I've done it!
Oh, my God!
This is so good!
Is it done?
Yes, I'm finished!
I love Sato!
The second one.
SatoSato
Emotional Fincial Ally.
Something handwritten
Suddenly, Mr. Tohoku
for supporting Hazuki Yuna.
Thank you very much.
I'll keep it up from now on.
Thank you very much for your support.
Let's go out to dinner sometime!
Wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
What the hell!
It's important, dinner!
He's just trying to be nice to one of us.
It's for everyone!
All of us!
If we all go out to eat together, we'll get to know each other better.
And our future will be brighter.
and our future will be brighter.
This is
Hinami's finished product.
This is so cute!
I love Sato emotion!
on a plate that says "I love Sato Emotion!
and a plate that says "I love Sato Emotion" on it.
Tart and Mario Hood
Marshmallows...
Is this wine?
Coffee.
For adults.
I'm sure it is.
It's like a dinner.
Like a dessert course.
It's nice to have something unique.
Yes, it does.
So, now that it's done...
Let's have Sato Sensei come over and present it to you.
Shall we present it to him and have him eat it?
I'll do that.
I hope he'll be pleased.
The director of Evins, Mr. Sato, is here!
Yes!
Hello!
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Today we have Inari and his wife here to talk to you.
They say you've been a regular customer of Evins.
Outrageous!
As a token of our gratitude
I made some homemade Valentine's chocolates.
They made it for us!
I'm so happy!
I'd like you to take it and eat it if you like.
Then, why don't we start with you, Kitami-san?
Yes! Like this.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you very much.
No, really.
I already have to thank you.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
Every single time.
You've made Ebbins so much fun.
On stage
And YouTube.
Every single time.
You've worked so hard to make this happen.
You can look forward to a return favor.
Aaaaahhh!
Noooooooo!
No way.
Wow!
I said it.
Maybe...
I told you where Evins is.
I said...
On fight day.
You're not going to give up the director's position?
But, Mr. director...
I still have to try it.
I can't taste it.
No, but I'm sure it's good.
Can you pass the chocolate?
Okay, then.
Are you sure you don't want some more?
As I'm explaining.
I'm sorry.
Take off your mask.
Okay.
Today's main dish is this...
Truffles.
Yes, yes, yes.
They look delicious.
Chocolate and regular truffles.
I mixed in some marshmallows.
I tried to make something creative.
And this one is a tart.
This is coffee, not alcohol.
Please don't worry about it.Don't worry about it, just drink it.
So that your child can work too.
Your concern. I appreciate it.
Yes, thank you.
Right away.
Bon appétit.
May I? Bon appétit.
Yum! Delicious!
Wow! Melt in your mouth!
Chicken meat! Really!
Really? Are you sure?
Delicious! I want to eat it all!
Are you sure?
No, it's good!
Oh, my God!
I wanted you to open this.
Can I open it?
What? What? What is it? What is it?
It's, um, a wish for Ms. Tsuchiya and Mr. Ewins to continue to be friends.
I made them engaged.
Wow! When did you get that?
Did you put it on her?
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, my fingers are a little short.
Oh, it fits!
It's the one!
Now, ah!
Everyone, the bond between Tsuchiya Fuku and Ewins is eternal!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm pretty sure I'm missing a finger, too.
Oh, no!
I'll kind of let you wear it when you're playing the game.
Don't get in the way.
Thank you very much. That's great.
Okay, let's go next, Yuna-san.
Okay, here we go.
Open!
And now, please wait.
May I have a moment? May I decorate?
This is S!
Sato!
K! Director!
Initials!
And even these roses.
I'll be happy to add them.
I'll read it then.
Happy Valentine's Day!
Dear Director Sato
I always appreciate
Thank you very much for your support
Thank you very much for your support.
I hope you will continue to support us
I look forward to working with you for a long time.
Let's have dinner next time!
Looking forward to it!
Whether you go or not, I will give you something in return.
But you know what, I'm rooting for everyone at Talk Not Live!
Yes!
I'm a box pusher!
They are all so cute, I can't stop looking at them, but I support them all.
I'm so happy! Thank you very much!
I hope you will keep coming to E-Beads.
I hope you will continue to visit E-Bee's and encourage us.
I hope you will continue to come to E-Beads and encourage us, and move forward positively step by step.
I would be very grateful if you could move forward step by step.
Yes, it would be my pleasure.
Yes! Let's get to it!
I made these truffles together with Norine's earlier.
So the taste is the same.
I see!
So, if you remember the taste from earlier...
The difference is this square one.
So, may I have this one?
Different? You mean it tastes different!
Yes, it is a little different.
A little different.
Yes, it tastes a little different.
Okay, I understand. Well, I'll have a sugar sa!
Thank you very much.
I'll have some sugar cane.
Yes!
I'll have a sugar cone.
Why are you laughing?
No, no, I just thought it looked good.
What do you think?
I can't really tell the difference.
What?
I made this one, this round one.
And I made this one, too.
If you like one better than the other one.
If you like one better than the other, can you tell me which one you prefer?
The round one or the square one?
Thank you very much.
I'll eat them all.
If you could tell me whether you prefer round or square...
I'd like to know that much.
Yes, okay.
Then which is your preference?So which is your preference?
The answer is 0.
Why?
Is there some deciding factor?
What is it?
Decide by judgment?
Yes.
Well, I mean, this one has a better mouthfeel.
Oh!
Wow!
The mouthfeel?
Yeah.
Mouthfeel.
Mouthfeel?
It was mouth-watering.
Oh, come on, you're trying to be funny.
No, no, no, no, no.
What would have happened if I had picked the square one?
Uh, well, actually, the square one...
Yeah.
Only this one.
It's a restricted item to begin with.
Oh, that's why.
And you just said it's a mouthful, didn't you? Yes, that's right.
This product is called "melt-in-your-mouth chocolat.
No, but, you know, this one is more mouth-watering. The round one.
I see.
Then, please change the name of this product.
This one is called "superior".
It's a little bit more rounded.
Really?
It tastes good that you made it only for yourself.
I'm so happy.
No, it really tastes good this way. It tastes better round.
Yay!
I'm sure Tohoku-san will be doing a lot of things for us in the future.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes. This is really the only facility that is so kind to us.
Well, we are very grateful if you say so.
Our books are very welcome.
Yes.
Endochene is a company that is committed to doing whatever we can to make the E-Binz building a better place to live.
In a sense, it's one of our slogans to do whatever we can to make the building called E-Binz a place to live.
Yes.
There are various restrictions.
If such compliance is done, then it is good that we all think about what we can do together to make it more exciting.
Then I hope you will continue to like the Iginari Expedition from now on, and if you have any problems, please consult with Captain Sato.
If you have any problems, please contact Captain Sato.
Yes, please look forward to it.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you very much for today.
We look forward to working with you again.
And that's all for the Igirinari Expedition!
Bye-bye!